(Raj:)Ironic, isn't it?
[WHISPERS]
Elevator shaft.
SHELDON:
Help me open it.
(Howard:)Are you crazy? We can't go down
an empty elevator shaft.
If you don't wanna proceed,
then you forfeit the bet...
(Sheldon:)...and I'll take possession
of your Fantastic Four.
(Howard:)Let's open her up.
(Sheldon:)Are you bothered
that I can so easily manipulate you?
HOWARD:
Don't push me, Sheldon.
(Howard:)I may be small,
but I took kung fu when I was 13...
(Howard:)...and I remember a good deal of it.
(Sheldon:)Oh, really?
(Sheldon:)I grew up with an older brother
and a very contentious twin sister.
And I could easily best you
in any physical confrontation.
(Sheldon:)Be it noogies, swirlies or the classic,
"Why are you hitting yourself?"
(Raj:)Ooh. Big talk from a man who was once
treed by a chicken.